A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3 FA456
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 3; 10.8 Cubic Feet 9 record storage cartons.
  - NY, Albany, Red Room, men of different nationalities, Nelson A. Rockefeller, circa 1960; 1008.15/227 (Box 3)
  - NY, Saranac, Lake Placid, Photographs by John Griebsch, circa 1960; 1008.15/208 - 1008.15/218 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller at museum, unidentified others, circa 1960; 1008.15/205 - 1008.15/207 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Leland Aldrich, circa 1960; 1008.15/244 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller in formal clothes, circa 1960; 1008.15/195 (Box 3)
  - University of the Philippines, President Carlos P. Garcia, laying cornerstone for nuclear research center, 1960 January 22; 1008.15/241 - 1008.15/243 (Box 3)
  - Boston, Commerce Department of Radio, TV, and MP, Eleanor Roosevelt, 1960 February 14; 1008.15/245 - 1008.15/246 (Box 3)
  - 41st Annual Dinner of the American Legion Dept of NY, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 February 23; 1008.15/247 - 1008.15/249 (Box 3)
  - Irving Feist requests autograph from Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 March 31; 1008.15/233 (Box 3)
  - University of Chicago Convocation, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 May 1; 1008.15/149 (Box 3)
  - Cornell University, Geneva Experiment Station Dedication, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 May 5; 1008.15/237 - 1008.15/240 (Box 3)
  - Albany, Reception for Major General O'Hara, 1960 March 21; 1008.15/236 (Box 3)
  - Japan Society Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Former Prime Minister Yoabida, 1960 May 23; 1008.15/226 (Box 3)
  - Hotel New Yorker, Nelson A. Rockefeller and Alexander Gross, 1960 May 24; 1008.15/219 - 1008.15/221 (Box 3)
  - Waterton National Park, Canada, Governor's Conference, Glacier National Park, Montana, Nelson A. Rockefeller playing golf, 1960 June; 1008.15/79 - 1008.15/80 (Box 3)
  - Many Glacier Hotel, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Moncure Cockrell, Conrad Wirth, 1960 June; 1008.15/145 - 1008.15/51 (Box 3)
  - South Fallsburg, NY, Lions Convention, 1960 June 6; 1008.15/1323 - 1008.15/1324 (Box 3)
  - Brooklyn Sunday School Parade, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 June 9; 1008.15/222 - 1008.15/225 (Box 3)
  - Lake George, 1960 July; 1008.15/197 - 1008.15/201 (Box 3)
  - CBS Face the Nation, Walter Cronkite, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 July 3; 1008.15/147 - 1008.15/148 (Box 3)
  - Chicago, GOP Convention, 1960 July 19; 1008.15/150 - 1008.15/151 (Box 3)
    - Charlotte Paller, 1960 July 22; 1008.15/152 - 1008.15/153
    - Jean Sanders, Ginger Lorr, 1960 July 21; 1008.15/154
    - Dwight Eisenhower, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Sen Jacob Javits, 1960 July 27; 1008.15/155
    - Barry Goldwater shakes Nelson A. Rockefeller's hand, 1960 July 25; 1008.15/156
    - Barry Goldwater shakes Nelson A. Rockefeller's hand, 1960 July 25; 1008.15/157
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller wears Nixon hat, 1960 July 27; 1008.15/158
    - Governor of Oregon Mark Hatfield, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 July 26; 1008.15/159
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller shakes hands, 1960 July 23; 1008.15/160
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Frankie Wise age 2 1/2, 1960 July 23; 1008.15/161
    - Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller "Pat for First Lady", 1960 July 28; 1008.15/162
    - Shirley Fenner of Lea County, NM, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 July 26; 1008.15/163
    - Sheraton-Blackstone Hotel, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 July 19; 1008.15/164
    - Katherine Lindsay rides her donkey into the Rockefeller camp, 1960 July 20; 1008.15/165
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller arrive at airport, 1960 July 23; 1008.15/166
    - Congresswoman Jessica Weis, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 July 23; 1008.15/167
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Billy Hill, Sen Kenneth Keating, 1960 July 25; 1008.15/168
    - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, University of Chicago, 1960 July 23; 1008.15/169
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller speaks at first session of Republican platform committee, 1960 July 19; 1008.15/170
    - Shirley Field, 1960 July 20; 1008.15/171
    - Diane Nordin, Mrs. William G. Stratton, 1960 July 21; 1008.15/172
  - National Association of Secretaries of State Conference, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 August 24-27; 1008.15/81 - 1008.15/83 (Box 3)
  - Ralph Planteen, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 September; 1008.15/97 (Box 3)
  - Harrisburg-York Airport, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Francis Worley, Jr., 1960 September 10; 1008.15/123 (Box 3)
  - American Scandinavian Foundation 50th Anniversary, Metropolitan Club, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Crown Prince Herald, Lithgow Osborne, Eleanor Roosevelt, Norwegian Foreign Minister Rr. Hm. Halvard Lange, 1960 September 23; 1008.15/96 (Box 3)
  - Pontiac, Michigan, Campaigning for Nixon & Lodge, 1960 September 24; 1008.15/87 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Nigerian Trip, at the Home of Mr. R.I. Fleming, Bishop Awosika, Mrs. Benson, Honerable T.O.S. Benson, Aduke Howells, Dr. Geoffrey Fisher, Adetokunbo Ademola, Kojo Botsio, Imoro Egala, Joseph Palmer, Honorable RA. Njoku, Dr. Nnamdi Azikiwe, Mother Mary Bernard, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Shirley Cummings, Julius Nyerere, 1960 October 2; 1008.15/55 - 1008.15/66 (Box 3)
  - Long Beach, NY, "Thank You Trip," Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 November; 1008.15/43 - 1008.15/44 (Box 3)
  - Poughkeepsie, NY, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Hatfield, Lawrence Quinlan, 1960 November; 1008.15/40 (Box 3)
  - Rochester, NY, Nelson A. Rockefeller, children, 1960 November; 1008.15/38 (Box 3)
  - United Cerebral Palsy Ball, Mrs. Colan, girl, 1960 November 3; 1008.15/36 - 1008.15/37 (Box 3)
  - Nixon Rally, Richard Nixon, Pat Nixon, Ike Eisenhower, 1960 November 6; 1008.15/1325 - 1008.15/1337 (Box 3)
  - Lake George, NY, Photographs by Richard K. Dean, 1960 November 10; 1008.15/25 - 1008.15/35 (Box 3)
  - Waldorf Astoria, Women's Division of American Friends of the Hebrew University, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Marion Anderson, Mrs. Louis S. Guibel Jr., 1960 November 11; 1008.15/1338 (Box 3)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Joseph Gruss, Jackie Robinson, Mrs. Dagabert D. Ruues, 1008.15/1339
    - Mrs. Eugene Picker, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Marion Anderson, Mrs. Guibel, 1008.15/1340
    - Joseph Mazer, Minister Jaja Wachuku of Nigeria, 1008.15/1341
    - Mrs. Anne Peshkue, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Marion Anderson, 1008.15/1342
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Marion Anderson, 1008.15/1343
  - King Frederik IX and Queen of Denmark Visit Albany, 1960 November 22; 1008.15/7 - 1008.15/24 (Box 3)
  - West Point, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Major General Westmoreland, Cadet Bill Heiberg, Cadet Dick Knoblock, Colonel Lincoln, 1960 November 30; 1008.15/45 - 1008.15/50 (Box 3)
  - NY City, Biltmore, SDX party, 5 contact sheets, 1960 November 30-December 2; 1008.15/1344 (Box 3)
  - Bruno Newman, Monte Randall, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960 December 12; 1008.15/3 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Lt. Governor Wilson, Stanley Judkins, 1960 December 28; 1008.15/2 (Box 3)
  - New York, Albany, Red Room, Nelson A. Rockefeller, unidentified family, 1961; 1008.15/1264 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Federal Treasury Department, 20th Anniversary, US Savings Bonds, 1961; 1008.15/1259- 1008.15/1261 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1961; 1008.15/1257 - 1008.15/1258 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Montefiore Club, Mayor Chet Kowal, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Cooke, 1961; 1008.15/855 - 1008.15/856 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Melvin Baker, Charles P. Penney, Sr., 1961; 1008.15/1263 (Box 3)
  - USS Ranger, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Admiral J.H. Sides, 1961; 1008.15/1393 - 1008.15/1397 (Box 3)
  - Rockville Center, Delaware River Basin Advisory Commission, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Walter Phillips, 1961 February 1; 1008.15/1349 - 1008.15/1352 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Gioffre, Senator Meighan, Irving Walt, Port Chester Boy Scouts, 1961 February 14; 1008.15/1216 - 1008.15/1217 (Box 3)
  - Federal Club Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Bernard Newman, 1961 February 25; 1008.15/1345 - 1008.15/1348 (Box 3)
  - CBS' Face New York, Commerce Department of Radio, Motion Pictures and Television, Murray Davis, Arthur Massolo, Richard Bate, 1961 March 9; 1008.15/1353 - 1008.15/1354 (Box 3)
  - Niagara Falls, 1961 March 9; 1008.15/1271 - 1008.15/1272 (Box 3)
  - Waldorf Astoria, Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Minerva Goldwater, 1961 March 15; 1008.15/1265 (Box 3)
  - Public Utilities New Haven Rail Road, 1961 March 17; 1008.15/1267 - 1008.15/1270 (Box 3)
  - Albany, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1961 April 7; 1008.15/1266 (Box 3)
  - Buffalo, NY, Dedication at Buffalo University, 1961 April 20; 1008.15/1355 - 1008.15/1368 (Box 3)
  - Buffalo, NY, Dedication at Buffalo University, 1961 April 20; 1008.15/1369 - 1008.15/1392 (Box 3)
  - Better Hearing Week, 1961 May; 1008.15/1262 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Ben-Gurion, 1961 June 22; 1008.15/1255 - 1008.15/1256 (Box 3)
  - Niagara Falls, Mayor Keller, Mr. Davis, Captain Keech, Mayor Miller, 1961 July 6; 1008.15/1274 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller joins Albany Chamber of Commerce, Stanley E. Cox, 1961 August 1; 1008.15/1280 (Box 3)
  - Commerce, Department of radio, motion pictures and television, 1961 August 2; 1008.15/1279 (Box 3)
  - Rensselaerville Youth Camp, 1961 August 2; 1008.15/1275 - 1008.15/1278 (Box 3)
  - Boscobel, Cold Spring, NY, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1961 August 30; 1008.15/1281 (Box 3)
  - New York City, Ribbon Cutting at the opening of Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association, Edith Alexander, Joseph Davis, 1961 September 14; 1008.15/1398 - 1008.15/1399 (Box 3)
  - Rochester, NY, Nelson A. Rockefeller visits Eastman Kodak Company, 1961 September 14 (Box 3)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Thomas F. Robertson, Director of Public Relations, 1008.15/701
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Thomas J. Hargrave, Keith S. McHugh, 1008.15/702
    - William S. Vaughn, Eastman Kodak President; Nelson A. Rockefeller, Thomas J. Hargrave, 1008.15/703 1008.15/704 - 1008.15/705
    - Commissioner McHugh, Edward P. Curtis, 1008.15/706
    - Mr. Vaughn, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mr. Hargrave, 1008.15/707 - 1008.15/711
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Kodak employee John D. Rockefeller, 1008.15/712
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Herman H. Waggershauser, 1008.15/713 - 1008.15/715
  - Brooklyn, Union Labels and Service Trades Council of Greater NY and Long Island, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Eli Danzig, 1961 September 25; 1008.15/1282 (Box 3)
  - Thank you trip to Oneonta, NY, SUNY Oneonta, 1961 September 25; 1008.15/919 - 1008.15/927 (Box 3)
  - Concordia College, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Steve Dahl, 1961 September 26; 1008.15/1283 (Box 3)
  - Hancock Field, Syracuse, Air National Guard, Major General O'Hara, Major General Lewis A. Curtis, Captain Edward Sugarman, Major General William P. Fisher, General Dissoway, 1961 October 1; 1008.15/1400 - 1008.15/1409 (Box 3)
  - Cooperative Grange League, Federation Exchange Inc., Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1961 October 5; 1008.15/1284 (Box 3)
  - Pulaski Day, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Lefkowitz, Neil Gallagher, 1961 October 17; 1008.15/1286 (Box 3)
  - Clipper Club, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John R. Anderson, 1961 October 18; 1008.15/1287 (Box 3)
  - NYS. AIDA Amendment 4 Jobs, 1961 October 18; 1008.15/1410- 1008.15/1415 (Box 3)
  - Waldorf Astoria Hotel, Bar mitzvah of Robert Meyer Wasserman, 1961 November 5; 1008.15/847 - 1008.15/849 (Box 3)
  - Robert A. Taft Institute of Government, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Preston Davie, 1961 November 10; 1008.15/1288 (Box 3)
  - Steuben Parade, 1961 December 4; 1008.15/918 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller boarding airplane, 1961 December 11; 1008.15/916 - 1008.15/917 (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Alvin Graham, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1961 December 13; 1008.15/915 (Box 3)
  - Princeton, N.J., Delaware River Basin Commission, Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Lawrence, Stewart Ludall, Robert Meyner, General Lack, Governor Carvel, 1961 December 13; 1008.15/894 - 1008.15/895 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, talking to crowd from a flatbed truck, 1961 December 18; 1008.15/908 - 1008.15/914 (Box 3)
  - "Lefkowitz for Mayor" Eisenhower, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1961 December 19; 1008.15/897 - 1008.15/907 (Box 3)
  - Medical Education Committee, Dr. Ewald Nyguisto, Dr. William Willard, Mr. Malcolm Muir, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Carl Pforzheimer, Dr. Hillebor, Dr. Ronan, 1962; 1008.15/1242 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, John Glenn, 1962; 1008.15/853 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, unidentified couple, 1962; 1008.15/854 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Jim Desmond, 1962; 1008.15/1160 - 1008.15/1161 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Joseph Feily, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John DeGraff, 1962; 1008.15/1243 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Ticonderoga boy scout troop, 1962; 1008.15/1098 - 1008.15/1102 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, blurry photos, circa 1962; 1008.15/578 - 1008.15/579 (Box 3)
  - Spelman College, Atlanta, Georgia, circa 1962; 1008.15/928 - 1008.15/938 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Mansion, 1962 January 1; 1008.15/1244 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, swearing in Fred Young as Court of Claims judge, 1962 January 2; 1008.15/1240 - 1008.15/1241 (Box 3)
  - University of Nevada, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dr. Alex DiCesena, 1962 January 4; 1008.15/896 (Box 3)
  - NY City, 39th Annual Meeting, International Benjamin Franklin Society Brig. General George Bliss, Samuel Chernoble, Ferdy Tagle, 1962 January 20; 1008.15/857 - 1008.15/860 (Box 3)
  - Seattle, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Hal D. Martland, 1961 January 21; 1008.15/893 (Box 3)
  - Lefkowitz for Mayor Campaign, 1962 January 29; 1008.15/888 - 1008.15/892 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, NYS. Nurses Association, 1962 January 29; 1008.15/1225 - 1008.15/1226 (Box 3)
  - Albany, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Speaker Carlino, Assemblyman Huntington, Senator Barrett, 1962 January 30; 1008.15/1209 (Box 3)
  - Albany, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Hatfield, Columbia County Students, 1962 January 30; 1008.15/1210 (Box 3)
  - Albany, Art Exhibit, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Hanks and son, 1962 January 30; 1008.15/1211 (Box 3)
  - Albany, Art Exhibit, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Adams' son, 1962 January 30; 1008.15/1212 - 1008.15/1213 (Box 3)
  - Albany, Art Exhibit, Assemblyman Travia, Mr. Carata, 1962 January 30; 1008.15/1214 (Box 3)
  - Albany, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Peset, Central School Wyoming County students, 1962 January 30; 1008.15/1215 (Box 3)
  - Ernie Davis Day, Elmira Salutes Ernie Davis, 1962 February 3; 1008.15/861 - 1008.15/862 (Box 3)
  - Connecticut GOP Victory party, Ed May, Jack Tifnery, Henry Shiembob, 1962 February 5; 1008.15/863 - 1008.15/887 (Box 3)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Mr. Coutaurier, 1962 February 5; 1008.15/1130 -1008.15/1133 (Box 3)
  - Museum Room, Restored Civil War Flags Ceremony, 1962 February 5; 1008.15/1218 - 1008.15/1222 (Box 3)
  - Museum Room, Restored Civil War Flag Hanging Ceremony, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Barrett, Senator Anderson, Assemblyman Mason, Major General O'Hara, Brig. General Stevenson, Josephine Roser, Malcolm Wilson, 1962 February 5; 1008.15/1200 - 1008.15/1208 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Peterson, School Group, 1962 February 5; 1008.15/1126 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller presents gift to Israeli representative, 1962 February 5; 1008.15/1127- 1008.15/1129 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, New Jersey Legislators, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1168 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs proclamation for National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1169 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Onondaga County girl scouts, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1170 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Onondaga County girl scouts, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1171 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Onondaga County girl scouts, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1172 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, United Federation of Teachers Representatives, Alice Marsh, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1173 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Professional Women's Club, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1174 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Duryea, Montauk students, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1175 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Westchester County Teenage Association Republican Organization, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1176 - 1008.15/1181 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Trillard, Nunde High School History Club, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1182 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Rockland County Artist, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1183 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Lincoln's Birthday Commemoration, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dr. Harlan Hoyt Horner, Bruce Catton, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1191 - 1008.15/1199 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Council of Churches, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1164 - 1008.15/1166 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Civil War Medallion, Dr. Harlow Hoyt Horner, 1962 February 12; 1008.15/1167 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Republican Club, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1227 - 1008.15/1229 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Brazilian students from Union College, Senator Begley, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1230 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Berkowitz, Hoosick Falls students, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1231 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Michaels, Cayuga County students, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1232 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman K. Wilson, St. Joseph's in Kingston students, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1233 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Beckowitz, St. Mary's Hoosick Falls students, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1234 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Junior Achievement Award recipients, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1235 - 1008.15/1238 (Box 3)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John Amstaz, Peter Atigan, Salvation Army, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1239 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Malcolm Wilson, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Rita Develin, Theodore Baillett, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1162 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Uruguayan students from New Paltz, 1962 February 13; 1008.15/1163 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblywoman Aileen Ryan and nieces, 1962 February 19; 1008.15/1184 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Kenneth Powers, Mrs. Norman Hosier, NY Division of American Association of University Women, 1962 February 19; 1008.15/1185 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, St. John's Students from Jamaica, 1962 February 19; 1008.15/1186 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman S.A. Spiegel and family, 1962 February 19; 1008.15/1187 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mackrate, Orest Maresca, Senator James S. Wastson, Senator Ernest D. Hatfield, Daniel G. Albert, Anthony Barbiero, 1962 February 19; 1008.15/1188 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, student contestants on Good Government Contest Sponsored by Albany County Women's Republican Club, 1962 February 19; 1008.15/1189 - 1008.15/1190 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Hughes and girl scouts, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1134 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mr. Bauer, Mr. Luebke, student from Mill Neck Manor Lutheran School for Deaf Children, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1135 - 1008.15/1138 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Representative Abner Sibal, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1139 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Pocantico Hills students, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1140 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Chase, Minoa students, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1141 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, African American group, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1142 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Grover, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1143 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Hudson, Uncle Sam Medallion, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1144 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Tyler, Canastota High students, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1145 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Speaker Carling, Long Beach students, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1146 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Feinberg, Artists Unit, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1147 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman McClaskey, Senator Conklin, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1148 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Senator Mitchell, Commerce and Industry Plaque, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1149 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Albany students, 1962 February 20; 1008.15/1150 (Box 3)
  - Ten Eyck- Fort Orange Room, Group of Republican Women, 1962 February 26; 1008.15/1151 - 1008.15/1152 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Barbiero, winners of "Know your Government," Contest from West Hempstead Junior High, 1962 February 26; 1008.15/1153 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Farm Conference Board, 1962 February 26; 1008.15/1154 - 1008.15/1155 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. National Honor Society Shaker High School, 1962 February 26; 1008.15/1156 (Box 3)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Bertram Baker and grandchildren, 1962 February 26; 1008.15/1157 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Institute of Corporation Law, 1962 February 26; 1008.15/1158 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Michaels, Kings Ferr students, 1962 February 26; 1008.15/1159 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Hempstead School Group, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1015 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Miss Johnson from Watertown, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1083 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Senator Condon, Yonkers students, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1084 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Senator Paine, Wealtha Sauerbrey, Ballston Spa students, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1085 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman McCloskey, East Meadow students, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1086 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Duryes, East Hampton students, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1087 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Bernstein and family, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1088 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Tyler, Chittenang students, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1089 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Tyler, Canastota students, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1090 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Esser, Hartsdale students, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1091 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, West Berlin students, 1962 February 27; 1008.15/1092 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Wilcox, Watertown students, 1962 February 28; 1008.15/1093 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Wilcox, Watertown essay winners, 1962 February 28; 1008.15/1094 - 1008.15/1095 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Ed Cass and group, 1962 February 28; 1008.15/1096 - 1008.15/1097 (Box 3)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Nowicki, Rockland students, 1962 March 5; 1008.15/1103 (Box 4)
  - Red Room. Senator Peterson, Wayne County church women, 1962 March 5; 1008.15/1104 (Box 4)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vassar students, 1962 March 5; 1008.15/1105 (Box 4)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman V. Ingram, Potsdam students, 1962 March 5; 1008.15/1106 (Box 4)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mercy Secretarial students, Albany, 1962 March 5; 1008.15/1107 (Box 4)
  - Red Room. Signing of milk dating bill, 1962 March 5; 1008.15/1057 (Box 4)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Van Rensellaer, Skidmore College students, 1962 March 6; 1008.15/1108 (Box 4)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Louis Lefkowitz, 1962 March 6; 1008.15/1109 (Box 4)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Feinberg, Plattsburg Rotary Club, students, 1962 March 6; 1008.15/1110 (Box 4)